Guide to the Divinity School Records, circa 1920-2005 UA.19.01.0001
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Administrative Files, circa 1920-2005; 156 Linear Feet; 109 boxes
  - Accession A73-123
    - World Service Bulletin, 1952-1953 (Box 7)
    - South Carolina Conference, 1953-1956 (Box 7)
    - Southeastern Jurisdictional Conference Correspondence, 1954-1956 (Box 7)
    - Special Committee of A.M.T.S., 1954 (Box 7)
    - W.A. Stanbury, 1954 (Box 7)
    - Study Committee on New Seminaries, 1953 (Box 7)
    - Survey of Theological Education in the U.S. and Canada, 1954-1955 (Box 7)
    - Theological Program (Rockefeller Brothers Fellowship), 1955 (Box 7)
    - The University Council, 1953-1954 (Box 7)
    - Virginia Conference: Alumni Scholarship Fund, 1954-1957 (Box 7)
    - B - Miscellaneous, 1954-1956 (Box 7)
    - C - Miscellaneous, 1953-1956 (Box 7)
    - D - Miscellaneous, 1953-1956 (Box 7)
    - E - Miscellaneous, 1953-1956 (Box 7)
    - F - Miscellaneous, 1953-1956 (Box 7)
    - G - Miscellaneous, 1953-1956 (Box 7)
    - H - Miscellaneous, 1953-1956 (Box 7)
    - I - Miscellaneous, 1953-1956 (Box 7)
    - J - Miscellaneous, 1953-1956 (Box 7)
    - K - Miscellaneous, 1953-1956 (Box 7)
    - L - Miscellaneous, 1953-1956 (Box 7)
    - M - Miscellaneous, 1953-1956 (Box 7)
    - N - Miscellaneous, 1953-1956 (Box 7)
    - P, Q - Miscellaneous, 1953-1956 (Box 7)
    - R - Miscellaneous, 1953-1956 (Box 7)
    - S - Miscellaneous, 1953-1956 (Box 7)
    - T - Miscellaneous, 1953-1956 (Box 7)
    - Positions Available, 1956-1957 (Box 7)
    - American Association of Theological Schools (2 Folders), 1952-1956 (Box 7)
    - Approved Supply Pastors' School (2 Folders), 1953-1957 (Box 7)
    - Board of Education of the Methodist Church Division of Educational Institutions, Section of Ministerial Education, 1953-1956 (Box 8)
    - Phillips Brooks Club, 1951-1954 (Box 8)
    - Calendar of Duke University, 1956-1957 (Box 8)
    - Calendar of Notices, 1957-1958 (Box 8)
    - Calendar of Special Events, 1954-1955 (Box 8)
    - Christian Convocation, 1956 (Box 8)
    - Christian Horizons, 1954 (Box 8)
    - The Circuit Rider, 1955-1956 (Box 8)
    - Christian Convocation, 1955 (Box 8)
    - Divinity School Lectures, 1956-1957 (Box 8)
    - The Divinity School Library Lectures, 1953-1956 (Box 8)
    - Dr. Maldwyn Edwards, Birmingham, England, 1955 (Box 8)
    - Emory Mother, 1956 (Box 8)
    - Financial Studies, 1951-1952 (Box 8)
    - General Information, 1955-1956 (Box 8)
    - George Hedley, Gray Lecturer, 1955 (Box 8)
    - Charles Gilkey, Gray Lecturer, 1953-1957 (Box 8)
    - Dr. Dillon Holt, 1955-1956 (Box 8)
    - Instructions for Addressograph, undated (Box 8)
    - Library Lecture - Bishop Rasha Manikam, 1958 (Box 8)
    - List of Learned Societies, 1953-1954 (Box 8)
    - Thomas B. Lugg, 1954 (Box 8)
    - Mrs. Mary Ely Lyman - Library Lecturer, 1955 (Box 8)
    - Dr. Gerald McCulloh (Board of Education) (2 Folders), 1955-1958 (Box 8)
    - Men's Grad Center (Correspondence, Etc.), 1952-1953 (Box 8)
    - Methodist Theological Schools (2 Folders), 1954-1955 (Box 8)
    - Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1953-1955 (Box 8)
    - N.C. Conference, 1953-1955 (Box 8)
    - Hanging of Portraits (University Committee), 1956 (Box 8)
    - Positions Available, 1957-1958 (Box 8)
    - Readers (2 Folders), 1956-1958 (Box 8)
    - Remedial English, 1955 (Box 8)
    - Research Council, 1955 (Box 8)
    - W.A. Rush Financial Reports, 1950-1951 (Box 8)
    - Scholarships, 1955 (Box 8)
    - Selective Service Materials, 1953 (Box 8)
    - Social Security Correspondence and Material, 1951-1955 (Box 8)
    - Ralph Sockman, 1950 Gray Lecturer, 1949-1953 (Box 8)
    - Student Recruitment, Adrian College, Adrian, Michigan, 1960-1967 (Box 8)
    - Student Recruitment, Albion College, Albion Michigan, 1960-1966 (Box 8)
    - Student Recruitment, Allegheny College, Meadville, Pennsylvania, 1960-1962 (Box 8)
    - Student Recruitment, The American University, Washington, D.C., 1959-1966 (Box 8)
    - Student Recruitment, Amherst College, Amherst, Massachusetts, 1964 (Box 8)
    - Student Recruitment, Arkansas St. Teachers College, Conway Arkansas, 1965 (Box 8)
    - Student Recruitment, Asbury College, Wilmore, Kentucky, 1963 (Box 8)
    - Student Recruitment, Athens College, Athens, Alabama, 1961-1967 (Box 8)
    - Student Recruitment, Atlantic Christian College, Wilson, NC, 1959-1961 (Box 8)
    - Student Recruitment, Auburn University, Auburn, Alabama, 1962 (Box 8)
    - Student Recruitment, Baker University, Baldwin City, Kansas, 1966 (Box 8)
    - Student Recruitment, Baldwin-Wallace College, Berea, Ohio, 1960-1967 (Box 8)
    - Student Recruitment, Baylory University, Waco, Texas, 1961 (Box 8)
    - Student Recruitment, Berea College, Berea, Kentucky, 1963-1965 (Box 8)
    - Student Recruitment, Birmingham Southern College, Birmingham, Alabama, 1960-1966 (Box 8)
    - Student Recruitment, Campell College, Buies Creek, NC, 1965-1967 (Box 9)
    - Student Recruitment, Catawba College, Salisbury, NC, 1964-1967 (Box 9)
    - Student Recruitment, Centenary College, Shreveport, Louisiana, 1961-1966 (Box 9)
    - Student Recruitment, Central Methodist College, Fayette, Missouri, 1964-1967 (Box 9)
    - Student Recruitment, Centre College of Kentucky, Danville, KY, 1964 (Box 9)
    - Student Recruitment, University of Chattanooga, Chattanooga, Tennessee, 1960-1967 (Box 9)
    - Student Recruitment, Claflin College, Orangeburg, S.C., 1966-1967 (Box 9)
    - Student Recruitment, Columbia College, Columbia, S.C., 1966 (Box 9)
    - Student Recruitment, University of Missouri, Columbia, Missouri, 1963 (Box 9)
    - Student Recruitment, Cornell College, Mount Vernon, Iowa, 1960-1962 (Box 9)
    - Student Recruitment, Cornell University, Ithaca, New York, 1961 (Box 9)
    - Student Recruitment, Dakota Wesleyan, Mitchell, South Dakota, 1963-1966 (Box 9)
    - Student Recruitment, Davidson College, Davidson, NC, 1964-1965 (Box 9)
    - Student Recruitment, Davis and Elkins College, Elkins, West Virginia, 1962 (Box 9)
    - Student Recruitment, DePauw University, Greencastle, Indiana, 1959-1966 (Box 9)
    - Student Recruitment, Dickinson College, Carlisle, Pennsylvania, 1961-1966 (Box 9)
    - Student Recruitment, Drew University, Madison, New Jersey, 1965 (Box 9)
    - Student Recruitment, Duke University Divinity School Dinner, 1965-1967 (Box 9)
    - Student Recruitment, Duke University, Durham, NC, 1960-1966 (Box 9)
    - Student Recruitment, Eastern Tennessee State University, Johnson City, Tennessee, 1963 (Box 9)
    - Student Recruitment, Elon College, Elon, NC, 1964-1965 (Box 9)
    - Student Recruitment, Emory University, Atlanta, Georgia, 1963-1967 (Box 9)
    - Student Recruitment, Emory and Henry College, Emory, GA, 1959-1965 (Box 9)
    - Student Recruitment, Evansville College, Evansville, Indiana, 1960-1966 (Box 9)
    - Student Recruitment, Fairmont State College, Fairmont, West Virginia, 1962-1967 (Box 9)
    - Student Recruitment, Florida Presbyterian College, St. Petersburg, Florida, 1966 (Box 9)
    - Student Recruitment, Florida Southern College, Lakeland, Florida, 1959-1966 (Box 9)
    - Student Recruitment, Florida State University, Tallahassee, Florida, 1962-1966 (Box 9)
    - Student Recruitment, University of Florida, Gainsville, Florida, 1962-1965 (Box 9)
    - Student Recruitment, Garrett Biblical Institute, Evanston, Illinois, 1959-1960 (Box 9)
    - Student Recruitment, University of Georgia, Athens, Georgia, 1963-1967 (Box 9)
    - Student Recruitment, Greensboro College, Greensboro, NC, 1966 (Box 9)
    - Student Recruitment, Guilford College, Guilford College, NC, 1965-1967 (Box 9)
    - Student Recruitment, Hamline University, St. Paul, Minnesota, 1964-1966 (Box 9)
    - Student Recruitment, Hendrix College, Conway, Arkansas, 1960-1966 (Box 9)
    - Student Recruitment, Huston-Tillotson College, Austin, Texas, 1965-1966 (Box 9)
    - Student Recruitment, University of Illinois, Urbana, Illinois, 1962-1967 (Box 9)
    - Student Recruitment, Illinois Wesleyan, Bloomington, Illinois, 1959-1966 (Box 9)
    - Student Recruitment, Iowa Wesleyan, Mount Pleasant, Iowa, 1964-1966 (Box 9)
    - Student Recruitment, Johnson C. Smith University, Charlotte, NC, 1965 (Box 9)
    - Student Recruitment, Kansas Wesleyan, Salina, Kansas, 1959-1966 (Box 9)
    - Student Recruitment, University of Kentucky, Lexington, Kentucky, 1965 (Box 9)
    - Student Recruitment, Kentucky Wesleyan, Owensboro, Kentucky, 1960-1966 (Box 9)
    - Student Recruitment, Lagrange College, Lagrange, Georgia, 1965 (Box 9)
    - Student Recruitment, Lambuth College, Jackson, Tennessee, 1961-1966 (Box 9)
    - Student Recruitment, Lenoir-Rhyne College, Hickory, NC, 1961-1967 (Box 9)
    - Student Recruitment, Lycoming College, Williamsport, Pennsylvania, 1961-1966 (Box 9)
    - Student Recruitment, Lynchburg College, Lynchburg, Virginia, 1959-1967 (Box 9)
    - Student Recruitment, Marshall University, Huntington, West Virginia, 1961-1967 (Box 9)
    - Student Recruitment, University of Maryland, College Park, Maryland, 1961-1962 (Box 9)
    - American Association of Theological Schools (3 Folders), 1959-1963 (Box 9)
    - American Association of Theological Schools - Theology Masters and Doctoral Programs, 1960 (Box 9)
    - Divinity School Business, 1961 (Box 9)
    - Duke Endowment - Rural Church Building Program, 1959-1962 (Box 9)
    - Jernigan, Homer L., 1958-1959 (Box 10)
    - Methodist Association of Theological Schools, 1958-1960 (Box 10)
    - North Carolina Conference, 1952-1961 (Box 10)
    - Systematic Theology - Appointments (Albert C. Outler), 1959 (Box 10)
    - Tingue, Arthur, undated (Box 10)
    - University Council, 1956-1962 (Box 10)
    - Western North Carolina Conference, Prior to 1960, 1953-1960 (Box 10)
    - Unlabeled Folder, 1956-1958, undated (Box 10)
    - A - Correspondence, 1957 (Box 10)
    - B - Correspondence, 1956-1957 (Box 10)
    - C - Correspondence, 1956-1957 (Box 10)
    - D - Correspondence, 1956-1957 (Box 10)
    - E - Correspondence, 1956-1957 (Box 10)
    - F - Correspondence, 1956-1957 (Box 10)
    - G - Correspondence, 1956-1957 (Box 10)
    - H - Correspondence, 1956-1957 (Box 10)
    - I - Correspondence, 1956 (Box 10)
    - J - Correspondence, 1956-1957 (Box 10)
    - K - Correspondence, 1956-1957 (Box 10)
    - L - Correspondence, 1956-1957 (Box 10)
    - M - Correspondence, 1956-1957 (Box 10)
    - Mac/Mc - Correspondence, 1956-1958 (Box 10)
    - N - Correspondence, 1956-1957 (Box 10)
    - O - Correspondence, 1956-1957 (Box 10)
    - P - Correspondence, 1956-1957 (Box 10)
    - R - Correspondence, 1956-1957 (Box 10)
    - S - Correspondence, 1956-1957 (Box 10)
    - T - Correspondence, 1956-1957 (Box 10)
    - U - Correspondence, 1957 (Box 10)
    - W - Correspondence, 1956-1958 (Box 10)
    - X, Y, Z - Correspondence, 1956-1958 (Box 10)
    - Student Recruitment - Abilene Christian College, Abilene, Texas, 1961-1967 (Box 10)
    - Student Recruitment - University of Alabama, University, Alabama, 1963-1965 (Box 10)
    - Student Recruitment - Macalester College, St. Paul, Minnesota, 1966 (Box 10)
    - Student Recruitment - Ohio Northern University, Ada, Ohio, 1960-1963 (Box 10)
    - Student Recruitment - Northwestern Univerisity, Evanston, Illinois, 1962 (Box 10)
    - Student Recruitment - High Point College, High Point, North Carolina, 1960-1962 (Box 10)
    - Student Recruitment - University of Houston, Houston, Texas, 1961 (Box 10)
    - Student Recruitment - Howard University, Washington, D.C., 1961-1965 (Box 10)
    - Student Recruitment - Huntington College, Montgomery, Alabama, 1962-1966 (Box 10)
    - Student Recruitment - North Carolina Wesleyan, Rocky Mount, North Carolina, 1962-1966 (Box 10)
    - Student Recruitment - North Carolina State University, Raleigh, North Carolina, 1965 (Box 10)
    - Student Recruitment - University of Massachusetts, Amherst, Massachusetts, 1964 (Box 10)
    - Student Recruitment - MacMurray College, Jacksonville, Illinois, 1960-1962 (Box 10)
    - Student Recruitment - McKendree College, Lebanon, Illinois, 1962 (Box 10)
    - Student Recruitment - McMurry College, Abilene, Texas, 1961-1967 (Box 10)
    - Student Recruitment - Methodist College, Fayetteville, North Carolina, 1963-1967 (Box 10)
    - Student Recruitment - University of Miami, Coral Gables, Florida, 1962-1965 (Box 10)
    - Student Recruitment - Miami University, Oxford, Ohio, 1963-1966 (Box 10)
    - Student Recruitment - University of Michigan, Ann Arbor, Michigan, 1960-1964 (Box 10)
    - Student Recruitment - Millsaps College, Jackson, Mississippi, 1960-1966 (Box 10)
    - Student Recruitment - Morehouse College, Atlanta, Georgia, 1962 (Box 10)
    - Student Recruitment - Morgan State College, Baltimore, Maryland, 1961 (Box 10)
    - Student Recruitment - Morningside College, Sioux City, Iowa, 1963-1966 (Box 10)
    - Student Recruitment - Morris Harvey College, Charleston, West Virginia, 1962-1967 (Box 10)
    - Student Recruitment - Mt. Union College, Alliance, Ohio, 1962-1966 (Box 10)
    - Student Recruitment - University of Nebraska, Lincoln, Nebraska, 1964-1966 (Box 10)
    - Student Recruitment - Nebraska Wesleyan, Lincoln, Nebraska, 1964-1966 (Box 10)
    - Student Recruitment - Ohio Wesleyan, Delaware, Ohio, 1962-1966 (Box 10)
    - Student Recruitment - Oklahoma City University, Oklahoma City, Oklahoma, 1961-1966 (Box 10)
    - Student Recruitment - University of Oklahoma, Norman, Oklahoma, 1959-1966 (Box 10)
    - Student Recruitment - Pennsylvania State University, State College, Pennsylvania, 1966 (Box 11)
    - Student Recruitment - University of Pennsylvania, Philadelphia, Pennsylvania, 1961 (Box 11)
    - Student Recruitment - Pfeiffer College, Misenheimer, North Carolina, 1960-1967 (Box 11)
    - Student Recruitment - Princeton University, Princeton, New Jersey, 1961-1965 (Box 11)
    - Student Recruitment - University of Pudget Sound, Tacoma, Washington, 1962-1966 (Box 11)
    - Student Recruitment - Randolph-Macon College, Ashland, Virginia, 1960-1967 (Box 11)
    - Student Recruitment - Rice University, Houston, Texas, 1961 (Box 11)
    - Student Recruitment - University of Richmond, Richmond, Virginia, 1967 (Box 11)
    - Student Recruitment - Salem College, Salem, West Viriginia, 1959-1960 (Box 11)
    - Student Recruitment - Scarritt College, Nashville, Tennessee, 1963-1966 (Box 11)
    - Student Recruitment - Simpson College, Indianola, Iowa, 1964-1966 (Box 11)
    - Student Recruitment - University of South Alabama, Mobile, Alabama, 1966 (Box 11)
    - Student Recruitment - University of South Carolina, Columbia, South Carolina, 1964-1966 (Box 11)
    - Student Recruitment - South Florida University, Tampa, Florida, 1965-1966 (Box 11)
    - Student Recruitment - Southern Illinois University, Carbondale, Illinois, 1965 (Box 11)
    - Student Recruitment - Southern Methodist University, Dallas, Texas, 1962-1965 (Box 11)
    - Student Recruitment - St. Andrews Presbyterian College, Laurinburg, North Carolina, undated (Box 11)
    - Student Recruitment - Southwestern College, Winfield, Kansas, 1963-1966 (Box 11)
    - Student Recruitment - Southwestern University, Georgetown, Texas, 1959-1967 (Box 11)
    - Student Recruitment - Southwestern at Memphis, Memphis, Tennessee, 1963 (Box 11)
    - Student Recruitment - Stetson University, Deland, Florida, 1962-1967 (Box 11)
    - Student Recruitment - Swarthmore College, Swarthmore, Pennsylvania, 1961-1962 (Box 11)
    - Student Recruitment - Syracuse University, Syracuse, New York, 1961-1963 (Box 11)
    - Student Recruitment - Temple University, Philadelphia, Pennsylvania, 1961 (Box 11)
    - Student Recruitment - University of Tennessee, Knoxville, Tennessee, 1962 (Box 11)
    - Student Recruitment - Tennessee Wesleyan, Athens, Tennessee, 1963-1967 (Box 11)
    - Student Recruitment - University of Texas, Austin, Texas, 1961-1967 (Box 11)
    - Student Recruitment - Texas Christian University, Fort Worth, Texas, 1961-1966 (Box 11)
    - Student Recruitment - Texas Wesleyan College, Fort Worth, Texas, 1961-1967 (Box 11)
    - Student Recruitment - Tilton School, Tilton, New Hampshire, 1962 (Box 11)
    - Student Recruitment - Trinity University, San Antonio, Texas, 1965-1966 (Box 11)
    - Student Recruitment - Troy State College, Troy, Alabama, 1964-1965 (Box 11)
    - Student Recruitment - Union College, Barbourville, Kentucky, 1959-1965 (Box 11)
    - Student Recruitment - Valdosta State College, Valdosta, Georgia, 1963-1967 (Box 11)
    - Student Recruitment - Vanderbilt University, Nashville, Tennessee, 1966 (Box 11)
    - Student Recruitment - University of Vermont, Burlington, Vermont, 1965 (Box 11)
    - Student Recruitment - Virginia Military Institute, Lexington, Virginia, 1966 (Box 11)
    - Student Recruitment - Virginia Tech, Blacksburg, Virginina, 1966 (Box 11)
    - Student Recruitment - University of Virginia, Charlottesville, Virginina, 1959-1967 (Box 11)
    - Student Recruitment - Washington University, St. Louis, Missouri, 1962 (Box 11)
    - Student Recruitment - Washington and Lee University, Lexington, Virginia, 1964-1966 (Box 11)
    - Student Recruitment - Wake Forest College, Winston Salem, North Carolina, 1964-1966 (Box 11)
    - Student Recruitment - Wesleyan University, Middletown, Connecticut, 1963-1964 (Box 11)
    - Student Recruitment - West Liberty State College, West Liberty, West Virginia, 1962 (Box 11)
    - Student Recruitment - West Virginia Wesleyan, Buckhannon, West Virginia, 1959-1967 (Box 11)
    - Student Recruitment - Western Reserve Institute, Cleveland, Ohio, 1964 (Box 11)
    - Student Recruitment - Western Maryland College, Wesminster, Maryland, 1961-1966 (Box 11)
    - Student Recruitment - Western Carolina Teachers' College, Cullowhee, NC, 1964 (Box 11)
    - Student Recruitment - West Virginia University, Morgantown, West Virginia, 1959-1967 (Box 11)
    - Student Recruitment - Willamette University, Salem, Oregon, 1959-1967 (Box 11)
    - Student Recruitment - Wisconsin State College, River Falls, Wisconsin, 1965 (Box 11)
    - Student Recruitment - Wofford College, Spartanburg, South Carolina, 1960-1968 (Box 11)
  - Accession A78-11
    - Wilson, Jack, 1961-1962 (Box 11)
    - Wilson, Jerry B., 1962-1963 (Box 11)
    - Wlson, Mr. and Mrs. Kathopoli, 1969 (Box 11)
    - Wilson, Leighton M., 1965-1966 (Box 11)
    - Wilson, Ronald Lynn, 1965-1966 (Box 11)
    - Wimberly, Lorris, 1968 (Box 11)
    - Winegar, Grady Clarence, 1959-1966 (Box 11)
    - Winegar, Ottalee, 1963-1965 (Box 11)
    - Winter, David Earl, 1963-1965 (Box 11)
    - Wise, Denny C., 1966-1968 (Box 11)
    - Withers, David Bruce, 1968 (Box 11)
    - Wiygul, Hershel, 1966-1970 (Box 11)
    - Wohlwend, Peter, 1966-1970 (Box 11)
    - Wolfe, William L., 1967 (Box 11)
    - Wood, Roger W., 1963-1965 (Box 11)
    - Woodard, Louis Herman, 1962-1966 (Box 11)
    - Woodard, James Richard, 1963-1965 (Box 11)
    - Woodruff, Charles, 1966-1969 (Box 11)
    - Worthy, Carl M., 1966-1969 (Box 11)
    - Wortman, Manual, 1963-1967 (Box 11)
  - Accession A56-698
    - Photographs - Rural North Carolina Churches, (2 Folders) 1924-1943, undated (Box 12)
    - Photographs - Church Building, Western North Carolina, undated (Box 12)
    - Miscellaneous Images of Churches, undated (Box 12)
  - Accession A78-11
    - Wright, W. Franklin Jr., 1964-1965 (Box 13)
    - Wright, Harold, 1960-1962 (Box 13)
    - Yarbrough, Jack B., 1958-1959 (Box 13)
    - Young, John K., 1966-1967 (Box 13)
    - Yount, David A., 1958-1962 (Box 13)
    - Yow, Thomas S., 1967-1969 (Box 13)
    - Yun, Nyung Ok, 1968-1969 (Box 13)
    - Zellner, James Hubert, 1959-1960 (Box 13)
    - Zikmund, Barbara Brown, 1962-1963 (Box 13)
    - Zinn, Grover, 1960-1961 (Box 13)
    - Zweitzig, Jerry W. 1969 (Box 13)
  - Accession A79-102
    - The Duke Divinity School Review, Winter 1966-Spring 1967 (Box 13)
    - The Duke Divinity School Review, Winter 1969-Winter 1977 (Box 13)
    - The Duke Divinity School Bulletin, 1937-1964 (incomplete) (7 Folders) (Box 13)
    - Langford, Thomas A. The Future of Academic Religion at Duke. (1970), 1986 (Box 13)
    - Planning for the Eighties, Institutional Advancement, University Relations, and Alumni Relations, 1979 (2 Folders) (Box 13)
    - University - Subcommittee Report, 1979 (Box 13)
    - Pembroke State University, Pembroke, North Carolina, 28372, 1976-1977 (Box 13)
    - Peace Research Society, 1972-1974 (Box 13)
    - Pacific Islands Seminar, 1981-1982 (Box 13)
    - Overseas Ministries Study Center, 1981-1982 (Box 13)
    - NC Drug Authority, 1973-1974 (Box 13)
    - University of North Carolina, 1976-1979 (Box 13)
    - Nixon Library and Archives, 1982 (Box 13)
    - National Humanities Center, 1980 (Box 13)
    - Fletcher Nelson, 1971-1981 (Box 13)
    - Inquiries Re: Positions, 1979-1981 (Box 13)
    - Helen Crotwell, 1974-1979 (Box 13)
    - Beth Mackie, 1973-1979 (Box 13)
    - Methodist College, Fayetteville, N.C., 1977 (Box 13)
    - The Methodist Theological School in Ohio, 1960-1969 (Box 14)
    - Lilly Foundation and Robert Lynn, 1972-1980 (Box 14)
    - Lawrence, James. Hollywood, California, 1974 (Box 14)
    - Joseph M. Kitawga, 1977-1980 (Box 14)
    - Huntington College, Montgomery, Alabama, 1973-1976 (Box 14)
    - Internationalization of Theological Education Proposal, 1978-1979 (Box 14)
    - Iliff School of of Theology, Denver, Colorado, 1970-1981 (Box 14)
    - The Hazen Foundation, New Haven, CT., 1975-1976 (Box 14)
    - William M. Finnin, Jr., 1977-1978 (Box 14)
    - Ethnic Minorities for Ministry, 1981 (Box 14)
    - England, 1980 (Box 14)
    - Ecumenical Institute for Advanced Theological Studies, 1981 (Box 14)
    - The Ecumenical Institute in the Holy Land, 1981-1982 (Box 14)
    - Ecumenical Institute for Advanced Theological Studies at Jerusalem, 1968-1977 (Box 14)
    - John Corey, Drew University, Madison, New Jersey, 1979 (Box 14)
    - Deans and Presidents of Seminaries Group, 1976-1978 (Box 14)
    - Deans and Presidents of Theological Schools, Meetings, 1977-1978 (Box 14)
    - Deans Search Committee, 1979-1980 (Box 14)
    - The Danforth Foundation, 1970-1976 (2 Folders) (Box 14)
    - John L. Crow, 1971-1980 (Box 14)
    - The Complutensian Polyglot, 1982 (Box 14)
    - Colgate Rochester Divinity School/Bexley Hall, 1970-1980 (Box 14)
    - Christian Sermon Society, 1975-1976 (Box 14)
    - Charismatic Movement, 1972-1974 (Box 14)
    - Brasher Project, 1982-1983 (Box 14)
    - Mrs. W.M. Boyst (Mary Martha Class) 1977-1978 (Box 14)
    - Boston Theological Institute, 1968 (Box 14)
    - Booth Ferris Foundation, 1975 (Box 14)
    - Marion B. Peavey, 1976-1980 (2 Folders) (Box 14)
    - Rufus H. Powell, 1967-1980 (Box 14)
    - Duke University Press, 1970-1979 (Box 14)
    - Duke Homesites, 198- (Box 14)
    - Drew, Thomas A. Graduate School of Business Adminstration, 1979 (Box 14)
    - Founders' Day Activities, 1980-1982 (Box 14)
    - Academic Council, 1976-1981 (2 Folders) (Box 14)
    - A. Kenneth Pye, 1970-1982 (2 Folders) (Box 14)
    - Alumni Adminssions Advisory Committee, 1980-1981 (Box 14)
    - Alumni Scholarship Committee, 1980 (Box 15)
    - William Bevan, 1979-1982 (3 Folders) (Box 15)
    - Young, Robert T., 1973-1983 (Box 15)
    - The Graduate Executive Committee, 1972-1980 (Box 15)
    - Institute of Polysciences and Public Affairs (Joel Fleishman), 1974-1978 (Box 15)
    - Wage and Salary Committee, 1979 (Box 15)
    - Harold W. Lewis, 1963-1980 (Box 15)
    - Personnel - University Policy, 1970-1979 (2 Folders) (Box 15)
    - Roundtable on Science and Public Affairs, 1975-1982 (Box 15)
    - James A. Ward, 1967-1982 (Box 15)
    - Watson Committee Report, 1969-1970 (Box 15)
    - Educational Facilities Committee, 1973-1976 (Box 15)